<Type Name="View" FullName="PepperSharp.View">
  <TypeSignature Language="C#" Value="public class View : PepperSharp.Resource" />
  <TypeSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".class public auto ansi beforefieldinit View extends PepperSharp.Resource" />
  <AssemblyInfo>
    <AssemblyName>Xamarin.PepperSharp</AssemblyName>
    <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
  </AssemblyInfo>
  <Base>
    <BaseTypeName>PepperSharp.Resource</BaseTypeName>
  </Base>
  <Interfaces />
  <Docs>
    <summary>To be added.</summary>
    <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
  </Docs>
  <Members>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public View (PepperSharp.PPResource viewResource);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor(valuetype PepperSharp.PPResource viewResource) cil managed" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="viewResource" Type="PepperSharp.PPResource" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="viewResource">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="ClipRect">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public PepperSharp.PPRect ClipRect { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance valuetype PepperSharp.PPRect ClipRect" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>PepperSharp.PPRect</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             ClipRect returns the clip rectangle relative to the upper-left corner of the module instance.
             
             This rectangle indicates the portions of the module instance that are scrolled into view.
             
             If the module instance is scrolled off the view, the return value will be (0, 0, 0, 0). This 
             clip rectangle does not take into account page visibility.Therefore, if the module instance 
             is scrolled into view, but the page itself is on a tab that is not visible, the return rectangle 
             will contain the visible rectangle as though the page were visible.Refer to IsPageVisible() and 
             IsVisible() if you want to account for page visibility.
             
             Most applications will not need to worry about the clip rectangle. The recommended behavior is 
             to do full updates if the module instance is visible, as determined by IsVisible(), and do no 
             updates if it is not visible.
             
             However, if the cost for computing pixels is very high for your application, or the pages you're 
             targeting frequently have very large module instances with small visible portions, you may wish
             to optimize further. In this case, the clip rectangle will tell you which parts of the module to
             update.
             
             Note that painting of the page and sending of view changed updates happens asynchronously. 
             This means when the user scrolls, for example, it is likely that the previous backing store of 
             the module instance will be used for the first paint, and will be updated later when your 
             application generates new content with the new clip.This may cause flickering at the boundaries
             when scrolling.If you do choose to do partial updates, you may want to think about what color
             the invisible portions of your backing store contain(be it transparent or some background color)
             or to paint a certain region outside the clip to reduce the visual distraction when this happens.
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CSSScale">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public float CSSScale { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance float32 CSSScale" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Single</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             CSSScale returns the scale factor between DIPs and CSS pixels.
             
             This allows proper scaling between DIPs - as sent via the Pepper API - and CSS pixel coordinates 
             used for Web content.
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="DeviceScale">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public float DeviceScale { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance float32 DeviceScale" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Single</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             DeviceScale returns the scale factor between device pixels and DIPs (also known as logical pixels or UI pixels on some platforms).
             
             This allows the developer to render their contents at device resolution, even as coordinates / sizes are given in DIPs through the API.
             
             Note that the coordinate system for Pepper APIs is DIPs.Also note that one DIP might not equal one CSS pixel - when page scale/zoom is in effect.
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="IsFullScreen">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public bool IsFullScreen { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance bool IsFullScreen" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             IsFullscreen returns whether the instance is currently displaying in fullscreen mode.
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="IsPageVisible">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public bool IsPageVisible { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance bool IsPageVisible" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             IsPageVisible determines if the page that contains the module instance is visible.
            
             The most common cause of invisible pages is that the page is in a background tab in the browser.
             
             Most applications should use IsVisible() instead of this function since the module instance 
             could be scrolled off of a visible page, and this function will still return true. However, 
             depending on how your module interacts with the page, there may be certain updates that you may 
             want to perform when the page is visible even if your specific module instance is not visible.
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="IsVisible">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public bool IsVisible { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance bool IsVisible" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Boolean</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             IsVisible determines whether the module instance might be visible to the user.
             
             For example, the Chrome window could be minimized or another window could be over it.In both of these cases, the module instance would not be visible to the user, but IsVisible() will return true.
             
             Use the result to speed up or stop updates for invisible module instances.
             
             This function performs the duties of GetRect() (determining whether the module instance is scrolled into view and the clip rectangle is nonempty) and IsPageVisible() (whether the page is visible to the user).
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Rect">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public PepperSharp.PPRect Rect { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance valuetype PepperSharp.PPRect Rect" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>PepperSharp.PPRect</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             Rect retrieves the rectangle of the module instance associated with a view changed notification 
             relative to the upper-left of the browser viewport.
             
             This position changes when the page is scrolled.
             
             The returned rectangle may not be inside the visible portion of the viewport if the module 
             instance is scrolled off the page.Therefore, the position may be negative or larger than the 
             size of the page.The size will always reflect the size of the module were it to be scrolled 
             entirely into view.
             
             In general, most modules will not need to worry about the position of the module instance in the 
             viewport, and only need to use the size.
             </summary>
        <value>The rectangle of the instance. The default return value for an invalid View is the Zero rectangle.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="ScrollOffset">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public PepperSharp.PPPoint ScrollOffset { get; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance valuetype PepperSharp.PPPoint ScrollOffset" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyVersion>1.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>PepperSharp.PPPoint</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
             ScrollOffset returns the scroll offset of the window containing the plugin, in CSS pixels.
             </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
  </Members>
</Type>
